Hi everyone , welcome to our reading time
大家好，欢迎来到我们的阅读时间
This is marina
这就是码头
Today we are going to read the little princ
今天我们要读一读小原则
Chapter ONE
第一章
Once when i was six years old
一次是在我六岁的时候
I saw a magnificent picture in a boo
我在一片嘘声中看到了一张宏伟的画面
Called true stories from natur
来自 natur 的真实故事
About the prime evil forest
关于原初邪恶森林
It was a picture of a boa constricto
那是一条蟒蛇的照片
In the act of swallowing an animal
吞食动物的行为
Here IS A COPY OF THE DRAWING
这是图纸的副本
In the boo
在嘘声中
It said : boa constrictors swallow their prey whol
它说：蟒蛇吞下他们的猎物 whol
Without chewing it
无需咀嚼
After that they are not able to move
之后他们就不能移动了
And they sleep through the six months that they need for digestion
他们睡过消化所需的六个月
I pondered deepl
我沉思着
Then over the adventures of the jungle
然后穿越丛林的冒险
And after some work with a colored pencil
在用彩色铅笔工作一番之后
I SUCCEEDED IN MAKING MY FIRST DRAWING
我成功地画了我的第一幅画
My join number one
我的第一名
It looked like this
它看起来像这样
I showed my masterpiece to the grown ups
我向大人们展示了我的杰作
And asked them whether the drawing frightened them
并问他们这幅画是否吓到了他们
But they answered frightened
但他们害怕地回答
Why SHOULD ANYONE BE FRIGHTENED BY A HAT
为什么有人应该被帽子吓到
My drawing was not a picture of a hat
我的画不是一顶帽子的图片
It WAS A PICTURE OF A BOA CONSTRICTOR DIGESTING AN ELEPHANT
那是一张蟒蛇消化大象的照片
But since the grown ups were not able to understand it
但是由于大人们无法理解它
I made another drawing
我又画了一幅画
I DREW THE INSIDE OF THE BOA CONSTRUCTOR
我画了 BOA 构造器的内部
So that the grown ups could see it clearly
这样大人们才能看得清楚
They always need to have things explained
他们总是需要解释事情
My drawing number two looked like this
我的第二幅画是这样的
The grown ups response this time was to advise m
这次大人们的反应是劝我
To lay aside my drawings of boa constrictors
放下我对蟒蛇的画作
Whether from the inside or the outside
无论是从内部还是从外部
And devote myself instead to geography
转而致力于地理
History , arithmetic and grammar
历史、算术和语法
That is why at the age of six
这就是为什么在六岁时
I give up what might have been a magnificent career as a painter
我放弃了本来可能辉煌的画家生涯
I had been disheartened by the failure of my join number on
我对我的加入号码失败感到沮丧
And my join number two
我的第二个加入
Grown ups never understand anything by themselves
大人自己永远无法理解任何事情
And it is tiresome for children to be always and forever explaining things to them
孩子们总是永远向他们解释事情是令人厌烦的
So then i chose another professio
所以后来我选择了另一个专业
And learn to pilot airplants
并学习驾驶 airplant
I have flown a little over all parts of the world
我飞遍了世界各地
And it is true that geography has been very useful to m
确实，地理对 m 非常有用
At a glance
一目了然
I can distinguish china from arizon
我可以区分中国和亚利松
If one gets lost in the night
如果一个人在黑夜迷路
Such knowledge is valuable
这些知识很有价值
In THE COURSE OF THIS LIFE
在今生的过程中
I have had a great many encounter
我遇到过很多次
With A GREAT MANY PEOPLE
与很多人在一起
Who have been concerned with matters of consequence
谁曾关心过重要的事情
I have lived a great deal among grown ups
我在成年人中生活了很多
I have seen them immediately close at hand
我看到他们近在咫尺
And that hasn't much improved by piling of them
而这种情况并没有因为堆积而得到太大改善
Whenever i met one of them
每当我遇到他们中的一个
Who seemed to me at all clear sided
在我看来，谁是完全清楚的
I tried the experiment of showing him my join number one
我尝试了向他展示我的 1 号加入的实验
Which i have always kept
我一直保持着
I would try to find out
我会试着找出答案
So if this was a person of true understanding
所以，如果这是一个真正有理解力的人
But whoever it was
但不管是谁
He or she would always say
他或她总是会说
That is a hat
那是一顶帽子
Then i would never talk to that person about boa constrictors
那我就永远不会和那个人谈论蟒蛇
Or prime evil forests or stars
或者为邪恶森林或星星
I would bring myself down to his level
我会把自己降低到他的水平
I would talk to him about bridge and golf , and politics and neckties
我会和他谈论桥牌和高尔夫，以及政治和领带
And the growing up would be greatly pleased to have met such a sensible man
长大后会很高兴遇到这样一个明智的人
Thank you for listenin
感谢您的收听
Next time we are going to read the chapter two
下次我们要读第二章
See YOU NEXT TIME BYE BYE
下次再见 再见